Guide to the William Hewlett Papers M1995
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
William Hewlett Papers
1907-2010
1960-2000
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Hewlett, William R.
William & Flora Hewlett Foundation
M1995
314 Linear Feet (714 manuscript boxes, 3 card boxes, 11 flat boxes, 9 record cartons, and 19 map folders)
The papers of William Hewlett document his professional and personal life, covering his many activities outside of Hewlett-Packard Company, how he invested his time and money, and his engagement with many organizations and individuals in business, politics, science, and academia.
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open for research, with the exception of a few boxes. Both Series 2: Financial and Series 4: Properties and Rentals each contain one box closed until the year 2050 because of sensitive material related to litigation. All items in Series 15: Audiovisual Materials were digitized and should be viewed or listened to through the reading room. The box containing the original audiovisual media is closed. Series 16: Original Correspondence is also closed to researchers, and only meant for use by staff, due to fragility; photocopies have been made available.
Note that material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use.
Scope and Contents
The William Hewlett Papers consists of correspondence, photographs, financial records, reports, minutes, calendars, notes, hardware, videotapes, compact discs, newspaper clippings, publications, and other materials. The collection documents some parts of Hewlett’s personal and professional life, as well as his finances, philanthropy, and engagement with scientific, cultural, international, business, and civic organizations. Some material in the collection was created and filed by staff and individuals representing the family after William Hewlett passed away in 2001.
Related Archival Materials
1. Cal Photos, University of California, Berkeley 2. California Academy of Sciences, Botany Collections 3. Dave Packard and Bill Hewlett: "Documentation" Videorecording, Stanford Special Collections and University Archives 4. Hewlett Collection, Agilent Technologies Company Archives 5. Hewlett-Packard Company Archives 6. Hewlett-Packard Ephemera Collection, Stanford Special Collections and University Archives 7. Packard Family Papers, Stanford Special Collections and University Archives 8. Uncommon Man Dinner, May 15, 1987 Videorecording, Stanford Special Collections and University Archives 9. William Hewlett Memorial Service Videorecording, Stanford Special Collections and University Archives 10. William R. Hewlett Library [electronic resource], Stanford Special Collections and University Archives
Biographical Note
William Hewlett was the co-founder of Hewlett-Packard, one of the most successful technology start-up companies in the history of Silicon Valley. He and his business partner and longtime friend David Packard flipped a coin to determine the order of their names when starting their company. Following the tremendous success of Hewlett-Packard, he became well known for his philanthropy, donating millions of dollars from his fortune to support various causes. In 1966, he and his wife established the William and Flora Hewlett Foundation. Today the private foundation is among the largest in the United States.
Arrangement
The William Hewlett Papers is arranged into 16 series, Series 1: General Correspondence, Series 2: Financial, Series 3: Memberships/Boards, Series 4: Properties and Rentals, Series 5: Biographical and Family History, Series 6: Subject Files, Series 7: Calendars, Series 8: William and Flora Hewlett Foundation, Series 9: Los Trancos Baseball and San Francisco Giants, Series 10: International Travel and Foreign Aid Trips, Series 11: Honors, Certificates, and Gifts, Series 12: Medical Records, Series 13: Collected Resources and Publications, Series 14: Hardware and Programming, Series 15: Audiovisual Materials, Series 16: Original Correspondence, and Series 17: Addenda 2016-122.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gifts of the Hewlett family, 2014. Accession 2014-001 and 2014-111. Addenda 2016-122 was donated in 2016.
Philanthropy -- History; Silicon Valley; Computer industry -- United States -- History; Science and industry.; Hewlett, William R.; William & Flora Hewlett Foundation; Chrysler Corporation; Packard, David, 1912-1996; Hewlett-Packard Company; Terman, Frederick Emmons, 1900-1982; Stanford University; Hewlett, William R.; National Academy of Sciences (U.S.); Oliver, Bernard M.; Hewlett, Albion Walter, 1874-1925; Hewlett, Walter B.; Institute of Radio Engineers; Carnegie Institution of Washington
- Series 1: General Correspondence, 1941-2001
  Scope and Contents
  Contains mostly letters, copies of outgoing correspondence, printed e-mails, and telegrams, interspersed with supplemental material, such as invitations, newsletters, newspaper clippings, photographs, notes, cards, and brochures.
  The series documents Hewlett's correspondence with friends, family, colleagues, acquaintances, organizations, academic institutions, and strangers. The content of correspondence regards Hewlett-Packard, events, general discussions, in-person meetings, business, family, travel, his personal life, and other topics.
  Arrangement
  Series 1: General Correspondence is arranged into two subseries. Subseries A: Alphabetical and Subseries B: Chronological.
  - Subseries A: Alphabetical, 1941-2001
    Arranged alphabetically by name or subject.
    Includes letters and messages sent to Hewlett, copies of outgoing responses, and supplemental material such as photographs, reports, and cards.
    - Abel, Dr. Shoshana, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Adams, Charles F., Raytheon Company, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Adams, Joseph C., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Adamson, Bruce Campbell, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Adrian Dominican Sisters, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Africa, 1973-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Akin, Dr. Gwynn C., National Science Board, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Albers, Donald J., Mathematical Associaton of America, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Albertson's Incorporated, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Alexander, Frank, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Allen, Ronald S., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Alliance to Save Energy, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Correspondence is addressed to David Packard. William Hewlett was blind carbon copied on his response.
    - Alta, Utah, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Alvarez, Dr. Luis W., 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Includes correspondence with Alvarez as well as his colleagues and widow after he passed away. Some newspaper articles about Alvarez are also present.
    - Amara, Roy, Institute for the Future, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - American Benefactor Magazine, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - American Cancer Society, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - American Electronics Association, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Includes correspondence and newsletters distributed by the American Electronics Association.
    - American Geophysical Union, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - American Institute of Engineers, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - American Leadership Forum, Silicon Valley Chapter, 1991-1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - American Red Cross, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - American Space Program, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - American University of Beirut, 1971, 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Ammen, Paul V., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Amplifiers, 1968-1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Anderson, Martin, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Anderson, Robert O., Atlantic Richfield Company, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Annual Report Lists (part 1 of 3), 1985-1999 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      Contains lists of individuals to send annual reports, and some personal responses from them sent to William Hewlett.
    - Annual Report Lists (part 2 of 3), 1985-1999 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Annual Report Lists (part 3 of 3), 1985-1999 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Ano Nuevo State Park, Elephant Seals Tour, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Arastradero Preserve, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Arbuckle Family (Ernest Arbuckle), 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Arin, Ei and Massy, William F., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Arizona State University, 1981-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Arnn, Larry P., President of the Claremont Institute, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Arnon, Stephen, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Aron, Nathan, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Art Works, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - ASARCO Incorporated, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Ashton, John O. and Hart, Jim, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Aspen Institute, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Assi, Ugo A., 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Assistant's Personal Notepad (11/9/82 - 5/5/83), 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Consists of notes written by Hewlett's assistant Madelan Schneider. Mostly records phone calls and messages, written mostly in longhand, partially in shorthand.
    - Assistant's Personal Notepad (5/9/83 - 10/11/83), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Assistant's Personal Notepad (10/12/83 - 3/29/84), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Assistant's Personal Notepad (3/30/84 - 10/18/84), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Assistant's Personal Notepad (10/19/84 - 3/25/85), 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Assistant's Personal Notepad (3/25/85 - 4/10/85), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Astending Institute, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Astronomical Society of the Pacific, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Athenstaedt, Dr. Herbert, Institut für Molekular-Physikalische Physiologie, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Atlas Economic Research Foundation, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Auger, B. Y., 3M Center, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Austin, Edward E., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      Correspondence is addressed to David Packard, William Hewlett was carbon copied.
    - Autographs/Pictures Requests (part 1 of 2), 1984, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Autographs/Pictures Requests (part 2 of 2), 1984, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Autographs/Pictures Requests, 1997-2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Automatic Meter Callibrations, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Babcock, Henry H., 1967 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Babcock, Horace W., Director of Hale Observatories, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Includes correspondence with 4 prints of astronomical photographs taken with the Carnegie Institution's du Pont Telescope in Chile.
    - Baber, Morris T., 1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Babson College, 1979-1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Includes correspondence sent by both William Hewlett and David Packard.
    - Bach Cantata Recordings, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Bachenmeimer, Ralph J., Corland Corporation, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Bacon, Rozawood, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Baer, Mark, Hewlett-Packard Libraries Manager, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Bailey, Dana, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Bailey, George D., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Bailey, Richard H., Century Mineral Corporation, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Bakar, Gerson, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Baker, Charles D., Pioneer Institute for Public Policy Research, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Baker, Charles D., Undersecretary of Health and Human Services, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Balbale, Mukhlis, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Baldwin, William, President of Kresge Foundation, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Balestra, P. H., 1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Ball, G. Victor, 1973-1995 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Ball, Margaret, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Correspondence is addressed to Mollie Yoshizumi, William Hewlett's assistant.
    - Bamman, Sam, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Bancroft Library, Oral History Project, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Barber, C. Bradford, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Barkley, Richard, Mary, and Alice, 1980-1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      Biographical / Historical
      Barkley family were neighbors of William Hewlett.
    - Barnes, Frank P., 1987 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      Barnes was also a student of Frederick Terman.
    - Barney Oliver Symposium, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Barton, V., 1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Bartride, Albert, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Bauer, Brunton, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Bay Area Corporate Two Percent Club, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Bay Area Council, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Bechtel, Steve, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Becker, Judy, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Becker, William, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Correspondence is addressed to John Young, William Hewlett was carbon copied.
    - Beckett, John C., 1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Beckman, Arnold D., 1985-2000 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Includes correspondence, articles, and a photograph of Hewlett and Beckman at a dinner preceding a Stanford Symposium.
    - Bedayn, Barbara, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Bell, Charles H., 1982-1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Belmore Browne Paintings, 1989-1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Belsey, James L., 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Bennet, George, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Bennett, George F., State Street Research and Management Company, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Benning, Arthur, 1979-1985, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Berent, Paul Alan, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Beroza, Paul P., 1988-1999 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Beyer, Laura M., 1983 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Biaggini, B. F., undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Big Sky of Montana, 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Bigler, William L., Jane, and Bobbie, 1979, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Bigus, A. W., 1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Bing, Peter S., 1997 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      Correspondence is addressed to Rosemary Hewlett.
    - Birnbaum, Joel, HP Labs, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Birthday Cards and Greetings, 1989-1998, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Bishop, June W., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Black Butte, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Blomquist, Herb and Pam, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Bogess, L. J., 1984 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Boise Cascade Homes, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Boniface, Robert L., 1996 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Bookbinding, Stanford University, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Books, 1967-1994, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Books Miscellaneous, 1965-1989, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Books Miscellaneous (part 1 of 2), 1989-1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Books Miscellaneous (part 2 of 2), 1989-1997, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Books Miscellaneous (part 1 of 2), 1993-1999, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Books Miscellaneous (part 2 of 2), 1993-1999, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Books Ordered, 1972-1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Books Received, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Books Received, 1981-1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Includes correspondence and photographs of William and Rosemary Hewlett with others on a day spent outdoors.
    - Books Received, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Books Received, 1992-1997 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Boone, William B., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Borden, Brownie and Richard, 1989-1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Bortz, Walter, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Boston Consulting Group Incorporated, 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Includes correspondence of both William Hewlett and David Packard.
    - Boulwere, J. H., 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Boyd, Berniece and Virgil, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Boyd, Leslie H., 1983, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Boys and Girls Club Dinner Honoring David Packard, Menlo Circus Club, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Braarud, Len, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Bradford Family, 1985-1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Brady, Robert J., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Braga, Gioia Marconi, 1993? (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Brandenburger, Roy L., 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Branscomb, Dr. Lewis M., 1983, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Breakthrough Publication, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Brewster, William S., 1979-1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Breymayer, Kurt, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Brian, Ray, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Briggs, Winslow R., Director of Plant Biology of Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Includes correspondence with Winslow Briggs and others regarding a reference for an appointment on the California state parks commission.
    - Brigham, Jack, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Bright, Rhinehart, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Brooks, Clyde, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Brooksby, Merrill and Foster, William G., 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Brower, David R., 1993 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Brown University, 1985-1991 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Brown University, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Brown, Allan F., 1992 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Brown, Joseph S., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Brown, Robert Minge, Douglas, and Harrison, 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Brown, Taylor, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Browne, Evelyn, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Brunner, Robert, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Buchhass, Carl, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Buck, Jane, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Bundy, Mary, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Bureau of Oceans and International Environmental and Scientific Affairs, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Burndy Library, 1976-1983 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Burnes, Irene, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Burns, David, Department of Conservation, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Burns, Gil, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Business Questions, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Business Week, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Buzard, Donald S., 1993 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Cabot, Louis W., 1980-1997 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Cabot, Thomas D., 1982-1988 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Caddes, Carolyn (part 1 of 2), 1984-2000 (Box 6, Folder 47)
      Includes correspondence as well as some photographs taken of William and Rosemary Hewlett for an article in Nikkei Business Magazine.
    - Caddes, Carolyn (part 2 of 2), 1984-2000 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Cafiero, Gene, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Calendars, 1993-2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Contains correspondence regarding calendars sent as gifts.
    - Califano, Joseph A., 1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - California Engineering Foundation, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Correspondence is addressed to Dr. William F. Ballhaus, not William Hewlett.
    - California Institute of Technology, 1970-1981 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - California Institute of Technology, 1989-1997 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - California Museum Foundation, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - California State Polytechnic University, 1967-1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - California State Universities and Colleges, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - California State University and Colleges Foundation, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - California State University, San Francisco, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - California State University, San Jose, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - California Wetlands and Waterfowl Program, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Cambridge University, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Cameron, Don, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Campbell, Tom, US House of Representatives and California State Senate, 1987-1998 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Canfield, Grant W., Hawaiian Educational Council, 1977-1994 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Capen, Richard H., Jr., Ambassador to Spain, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Card, Paul, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Cardwell, Susan M., 1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Caring People Magazine, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Carlson, Edward E., Chairman of UAL Incorporated, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Carlstrom, Theodore, Attorney at Law, 1981-1997 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      Ted Carlstrom was Hewlett's attorney for many years. Includes information on trusts, San Felipe Ranches, job references, and personal correspondence.
    - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Carson, Frances and Paul, 1961, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Carter Center, 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Carter, Edward, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Cash, Mary, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Castillo, Enrique, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Includes correspondence and a photograph of Hewlett visiting with young professionals.
    - Cazzaniga, Emanuela, Hewlett-Packard Milano, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - CDs, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Includes correspondence and lists of music, not actual compact discs.
    - Cedillo, Jose Luis Suarez, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - CEIP Fund Incorporated, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Center for the Study of Extraterrestrial Intelligence, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - CEO Consultants, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Challis National Forest, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Chamberlain Family, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Chan, Shu-Park, China Experimental University, 1985-1992 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      Includes correspondence with Shu-Park Chan, Clive Ainsworth, Chorkin Chan, and S. Y. Zee, Senator John Garamendi, and Theodore Calstrom. Some documents contain Chinese Characters.
    - Chance, Doug, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Chance, Dr. William M., 1986 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Chapman, Susan, Details Marketing Incorporated, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Chase Manhattan Corporation, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Chase, Richard, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Chen, Winston H., Solectron Company, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Chickering Company, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Chickering, Bebbie, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Chickering, Jean and Sherman, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Chickering, Sherman, 1971-1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Chickering, Sherman, 1985-1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Chinese Delegation Visit, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Christmas Card List (part 1 of 2), 1992-1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Christmas Card List (part 2 of 2), 1992-1997 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Christmas Card List, 1995-2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Christmas Cards, 1984-1992, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Mostly cards sent by Bill and Rosemary Hewlett. Some sent to them by other family members. Includes family photographs.
    - Christmas Thank You Correspondence, 1979-1993 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Christine, Mark, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Christopher, Warren, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Churchhill, Maria, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Claremont Graduate School, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Claremont McKenna College, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Clark, Clayton, Utah State University, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Clarke, Samuel T., Eastern Sales Region, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Clement, Carl J., Clement Designlabs, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Cloutier, John, Editor of Instrument News, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Coberly, C. Wheeler, Coberly and Associates, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Cochran, Edward, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Coffin, Ted, Corporate Library, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Includes some answers from William Hewlett on questions regarding personal and company history.
    - Coffy, Joseph, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Coffy was William Hewlett's former roommate at Stanford.
    - Cole, Dr. Kenneth S., National Institute of Health, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Coleman, Jay R., 1999 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Coller, Ethel C., 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Colliver, Gary and Reva, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Colorado Altitude Research Institute, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Colorado State University, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Columbia University, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Comman, Ron, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Common Cause, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Commonwealth Club of California, 1980-2000 (Box 10, Folder 19)